Resume

Linus Dagerfall Vinnå

Backvägen 9 137 57 TUNGELSTA 073-903 18 98 linus.dv@gmail.com

Summary

UX/UI designer with skills in requirement management and 5 years of experience in Android development. I have worked for 7 months at Qliro AB, where my area of responsibility has been designing with focus on the merchant's experience. For the moment I design a new platform that will help merchants with onboarding.

Work experience	
2024-04 – 2024-06	UX/UI designer Qliro
2018-01 – 2024-01	Android-developer Mathem
2017-06 – 2017-07	Summer job as presale IP-Only
2016-07	Summer job as presale IP-Only
2015-06 – 2015-07	Summer job as presale IP-Only
Internship	
2023-10 – 2024-04	Internship as a UX/UI-designer Qliro
2017-09 – 2018-01	Internship as an Android-developer Mathem
Education	
2022-2024	UX designer with requirements skills Chas Academy 300 YH-p
2016-2018	Mobile Application Development Nackademin
2013-2016	Technical program Nacka Gymnasium

Other merits

2022- On the board of the student union

Chas Academy

2022- Student representative

Chas Academy

Diploma

2018 **Degree certificate Mobile Application Development**

Nackademin

Language skills

Swedish - Native language

English - Very good in speaking and writing.

French - I can speak and write French to some extent.

Computer knowledge

References

Be provided on request.